linkxl.com 2009-08-19

# Privacy Policy - LinkXL Contextual Text Link Ads

| 

We understand and appreciate the fact that our customers are concerned about the privacy afforded to their information collected when dealing with LinkXL™.. We are committed to providing our customers with a high level of privacy in relation to the personal information that is collected whilst dealing with LinkXL™. To display this commitment, we provide the following privacy statement for our customer's viewing.

**Personal Information Collected**  
The type of information generally collected by LinkXL™ includes your name, address, telephone number, user messages, e-mail address, city, region and billing information in addition to tax information required by the IRS. This information is collected in order for LinkXL™ to perform the services that you have requested and to enforce the LinkXL™ User Agreement.

**Information Collected on this Site**  
When you look at this website, our Internet Service Provider makes a record of your visit. Also, the following information is logged, used, and monitored for statistical purposes, enforcement of the User Agreement and to facilitate member disputes.

· your server address  
· your top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, etc)  
· the date and time of your visit to the site  
· the pages you accessed and documents downloaded  
· messages you have sent via member messaging  
· the previous site you have visited the type of browser you are using  
· any other information we choose to collect in reference to any member accessing our website 

We do not use or disclose your personal information collected for any other purpose other than the primary purpose without firstly gaining your consent, or where it is required by law.

**Credit Card Information**  
LinkXL™ which is fully owned and operated by InConTXT LLC doing business as LinkXL™. LinkXL™ is aware of the potential risks inherent to online transactions. As such, we have the most advanced security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Authorize.Net encrypts your personal information with secure server technology using Secure Socket Layers (SSL). SSL software will encrypt (scramble your personal information so that it becomes illegible to everyone but LinkXL™) before it is sent over the Internet to our secure site. You will know if you have entered a secure page when an icon appears on your browser, either a key for Netscape, Firefox, or a lock for Microsoft Internet Explorer. 

Furthermore, each employee of LinkXL™ has been and will be made aware of security issues and practices as part of our extensive job training, and these practices are reviewed monthly at team meetings. As well, web security is reviewed ongoing. 

**Email**  
Your e-mail address is recorded when you register at the site. We respect the confidentiality of the information you provide to us. As such, any personal information that we collect will only be used for the purpose for which it has been provided to us. Under no circumstances will your e-mail address be added, sold or given to a mailing list or used for any other non-LinkXL™ related purpose or by approved partners without your consent being obtained or where it is required by law. 

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information  
**We do not use or disclose your personal information collected for any other purpose other than the primary purpose without firstly gaining your consent, or where it is required by law. In regard to our primary purpose, we act as an agent and we may disclose your personal information to the seller or purchaser of ads through our LinkXL™ system. 

**Personal Information Security  
**LinkXL™ is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and we will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration.

**Our Use of Your Information**  
We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, including user messages, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, services and to enforce the User Agreement. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet all members’ needs.

**Access to Personal Information**  
You can request us to provide you with access to the personal information we hold about you. If we are able to, we will provide you with access. A fee may apply to such access. If we deny your request for access, we will let you know why. Access is limited to our record of your address, contact details, photographic identification details, accounts with us and balances and statements relating to those accounts.

**Privacy Complaints**  
If you wish to make a complaint about any breach or potential breach of this privacy policy or the National Privacy Principles, you can contact us.

LinkXL.com, LLC  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
316-1/2 South Main St.  
Suite 204  
Royal Oak, MI 48067  

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
Our privacy agreement may change from time to time; any major change will be posted in the Privacy Policy section of the site.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

If you have any questions about our security & privacy policies, the practices of this site, or your dealings with LinkXL™, please contact: 

LinkXL.com, LLC  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
316-1/2 South Main St.  
Suite 204  
Royal Oak, MI 48067
